（过渡音乐）
(transition music)
- 将数据集上传到 hub。
- Uploading a dataset to the hub.
在本视频中，我们将了解
In this video, we'll take a look
如何上传你自己的数据集
at how you can upload your very own dataset
到 Hugging Face Hub。
to the Hugging Face Hub.
你需要做的第一件事
The first thing you need to do
是在 hub 上创建一个新的数据集仓库。
is create a new dataset repository on the hub.
所以，只需点击你的个人资料图标
So, just click on your profile icon
并选择 New Dataset 按钮。
and select the New Dataset button.
接下来，我们需要指定数据集的所有者。
Next, we need to assign an owner of the dataset.
默认情况下，所有者是你的 hub 帐户，
By default, this will be your hub account,
但你也可以
but you can also create datasets
以你所属的组织的名义创建数据集。
under any organization that you belong to.
然后，我们只需要给数据集起个好名字
Then, we just need to give the dataset a good name
并指定它是公共数据集还是私有数据集。
and specify whether it is a public or private dataset.
任何人都可以访问公共数据集
Public datasets can be accessed by anyone
而私人数据集只能
while private datasets can only be accessed
允许你或你的组织成员访问。
by you or members of your organization.
这样，我们就可以继续创建数据集了。
And with that, we can go ahead and create the dataset.
现在你在 hub 上有一个空的数据集仓库，
Now that you have an empty dataset repository on the hub,
接下来要做的是向其中添加一些实际数据。
the next thing to do is add some actual data to it.
你可以用 git 做到这一点，
You can do this with git,
但最简单的方法是选择 Upload file 按钮。
but the easiest way is by selecting the Upload file button.
然后，你可以继续下一步
And then, you can just go ahead
直接从你的机器上传文件。
and upload the files directly from your machine.
上传文件后，
After you've uploaded your files,
你会在 Files and versions 选项卡下
you'll see them appear in the repository
看到它们出现在仓库中。
under the Files and versions tab.
最后一步是创建数据集卡。
The last step is to create a dataset card.
对其他人来说，归档良好的数据集貌似更有用，
Well-documented datasets are more likely to be useful
因为他们提供了影响决策的上下文信息
to others as they provide the context to decide
包括数据集是否与需求相关
whether the dataset is relevant
或者有没有误差
or whether there are any biases
或使用该数据可能遇到的风险。
or risks associated with using the dataset.
在 Hugging Face Hub 上，
On the Hugging Face Hub,
此信息存储在每个仓库的 README 文件中。
this information is stored in each repositories README file.
你需要执行两个主要步骤。
There are two main steps that you should take.
首先，你需要创建一些元数据
First, you need to create some metadata
这将允许其他人在 hub 上
that will allow your dataset
轻松找到你的数据集。
to be easily found by others on the hub.
你可以使用数据集标记应用程序
You can create this metadata
创建此元数据，
using the datasets tagging application,
我们将在视频说明信息中包含它的链接。
which we'll link to in the video description.
创建元数据后，
Once you've created the metadata,
你可以填写数据集卡的其余部分，
you can fill out the rest of the dataset card,
我们提供了一个模板
and we provide a template
相关链接也会包含在下面的视频信息内容中。
that we'll also link to in the video.
一旦你的数据集在 hub 上，
And once your dataset is on the hub,
你可以使用可信赖的 load_dataset 函数加载它。
you can load it using the trusty load_dataset function.
只需提供你的仓库的名称
Just provide the name of your repository
和一个 data_files 参数，你就可以开始使用了。
and a data_files argument, and you're good to go.
（过渡音乐）
(transition music)